cheapdigitaldownload.com 2019-12-31

# Privacy Policy Cheapdigitaldownload.com

## **Introduction**

ALLKEYSHOP NETWORK provides Game comparison prices  websites that helps Customers compare and buy games at best prices. Allkeyshop Network gathers several sites specialized in the price comparison of video games as well as a site dedicated to its loyalty program [allkeyshop.com](http://allkeyshop.com/) / [Keyforsteam.de](http://keyforsteam.de/) / [Goclecd.fr](http://goclecd.fr/) / [CheapDigitalDownload.com](https://cheapdigitaldownload.com/) / [Clavecd.es](http://clavecd.es/) / [Cdkeyit.it](http://cdkeyit.it/) / [Cdkeypt/pt](http://cdkeypt/pt) / [Cdkeynl.nl](http://cdkeynl.nl/) / [Steamkeybox.com](https://steamkeybox.com/) Security & Privacy is an important part of our platform that we take very seriously. Therefore, this Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Allkeyshop Network website collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users of the [Allkeyshop.com](http://allkeyshop.com/) website and Allkeyshop Network. This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products or services offered by Allkeyshop Network. In order to ensure confidentiality and lawful processing of its, Visitors, Customers and Comparison prices websites Users personal data, Allkeyshop Network in its capacity of a data controller and of a processor, conducts its activities in strict compliance with the requirements set in the Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of this data (GDPR). This Privacy Policy applies to all Customers, Allkeyshop Network Users and Visitors of our Sites and Services.

##  **What Information We Collect and How We Use It**

We may collect the following types of information about you on our Website

###  **Customers and Visitors of our Sites**

We may collect your personal data in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when you visit our Sites, register on the Sites, subscribe to our newsletter, fill out a form, or in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available. **Registration and Contact Information:** As appropriate and depending on the Services you would like to use, Customers and Visitors may be asked to provide us with full name, username, email, address. **Technical, Usage and Location Information:** We automatically collect information on how you interact with the Site, such as the IP address from which you access the Site, date and time, information about your browser, operating system and computer or device, pages viewed and items clicked. We may also collect location information, including location information automatically provided by your computer or device. We use cookies and similar technologies to collect some of this information and persist your login to our Site. **Third Party Platforms.** We may collect information when you interact with our advertisements and other content on third-party sites or platforms, such as social networking sites. This may include information such as Facebook Likes, profile information gathered from social networking sites during signup or the fact that you viewed or interacted with our content. **Other Information.** We may collect other information from you that is not specifically listed here. We may use any such information in accordance with this Privacy Policy or as otherwise permitted by you.

###  **Giveaways and Loteries Users**

Users that use Giveaway and Loterie on Allkeyshop Network require to supply certain information as part of a Giveaway or loterie. Allkeyshop Network processes this data in accordance with our Privacy Policy. The reward program of Allkeyshop network is a consent based giveaway and loterie platform, this means that in order for us to process data on behalf of users they must provide it via explicit consent first. This might be as simple as filling out a form or something more complex like approve the Allkeyshop Network privacy policy. Name, Email & Form Fields: By default each Allkeyshop Network Websites may collect basic login information from users that includes their full name and email address. By entering in the Allkeyshop Network loterie and Giveaway you are accepting that Allkeyshop Network owners will have access to the information you provide. Some Giveaway may also require which include Date of Birth (for Age Verification) and other identifiable fields that the user can choose to fill out on external tools like the Giveaway tools Gleam. **Social Logins:** Allkeyshop Network also allows websites Users to connect social accounts to your profile. Allkeyshop users that have social logins enabled on their profil will be able to see basic information related to accounts that you connect. This includes but is not limited to your name, email address, social profile URL’s and associated profile photos.

  * Allkeyshop will only ever use information that you have made public or specifically allowed us to access when you accept permissions
  * Allkeyshop does not know or store any passwords associated with your social accounts

Allkeyshop Network does not track or provide any personal information to Companies until you explicitly provide consent. This means that you do not expose any personal information to Companies.

##  **Cookies**

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year. If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser. When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed. If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day. Allkeyshop Network use Cookies to track information about users in order to serve them content. This includes but is not limited to:

  * Persist Customers sessions that are logged into Allkeyshop Network Websites
  * Tracking and awarding Points and coins for referring users via our Reward program (loterie, Giveaway..)
  * Tracked users referred by our Referral Program

## **How We Use Collected Information**

Allkeyshop Network may collect and use User’s personal information for the following purposes:

###  **Allkeyshop Network Website Users**

  * To administer our Website and for internal operations, including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research, statistical and survey purposes;
  * To write or display content such as case studies or customer testimonials on our Site;
  * To improve Allkeyshop network Websites to ensure that content is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your Device;
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so;
  * To send periodic emails: We may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their profil. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests.

### **Allkeyshop Network Users**

Allkeyshop Network does not own or use any identifiable data provided users for any reason other than to:

  * Ensure that your specific request is carried out and assigned to the correct giveaway or loterie that you provided consent for
  * Identify and detect fraudulent behaviour or Allkeyshop Users that are violating our [Terms of Service](https://www.allkeyshop.com/blog/mentions-legales-pour-le-site-allkeyshop-com/)
  * Provide support to Customers regarding specific User queries
  * Analyze anonymized statistics or usage to help improve the Allkeyshop Network

## **Sharing Information With Third Parties**

We do not access, sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others.  **Customers and Visitors of our Site** Allkeyshop Network may use third party service providers to help us operate our business or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or collecting Website analytics. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission. Allkeyshop Network engages certain onward subprocessors that may process personal data submitted to Allkeyshop Network services. These subprocessors are listed below, and may be updated by Allkeyshop Network from time to time:

  * Google Analytics –  [Privacy Shield Certified](https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt000000001L5AAI)
  * MailChimp –  [Privacy Shield Certified](https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt0000000TO6hAAG)
  * G2APay –
  * Woocommerce –
  * Jeu.Video –
  * Steam
  * OneAllsocialLogin
  * Facebook
  * Google
  * hotjar.com

### **Third Party Websites**

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

###  **Legal Disclosures**

In certain limited circumstances, we may also have to disclose your personal data to public authorities and other third parties, if the disclosure is in response to lawful requests made by such public authorities, including to conform with national security or law enforcement requirements. Your personal information may also be disclosed to other third parties when compelled to do so by government authorities or required by law or regulation including, but not limited to, in response to court orders and subpoenas. Allkeyshop Network may also share personal data with third parties to prevent, investigate or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our Terms of Service or any other agreement related to the Services, or as otherwise required by law.

##  **Information Security**

We use appropriate technical and organizational security measures to protect any personal information we process about visitors to our Website against unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction. However, please note that no Internet transmission can ever be guaranteed 100% secure, and so we encourage you to take care when disclosing personal information online and to use readily available tools, such as Internet firewalls, secure e-mail and similar technologies to protect yourself online.

##  **EU and EEA residents**

The servers where Allkeyshop Network stores all personal data are located in the Europe.. If you are located in a country member of either the EU or the EEA, please be aware that any information provided to us, including personal information, will be transferred from your country of origin to the EU. Except in the case of data transfers under the EU-US Privacy Shield and the Swiss-US Privacy Shield, we may ask for your express consent to provide such data to us or allow us to collect such data.

##  **International Transfer of Personal Data**

All personal data we process is stored directly, without any subsequent transfers, on EU-based servers, which we loan from datacenter that is certified and adheres to the EU – U.S GDPR. To additionally guarantee to our Customers and their European users (data subjects) the legality of our processing services and the international transfers of the personal data, Allkeyshop Network has undertaken GDPR compliant contractual commitments, binding us, as a data processor, to protect the data privacy and to ensure the most adequate level of data security. Please note that the country where we operate may have privacy and data protection laws that differ from, and are potentially less protective than, the laws of your country. You agree to this risk when you create an account with Us and click “I accept Allkeyshop Network Terms of Service & Privacy Policy” to data transfers, irrespective of which country you live in. If you later wish to withdraw your consent, you can delete your Allkeyshop account directly on you profil page.

###  **Data Retention Periods**

Allkeyshop will not retain data longer than is necessary to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected or as required by applicable laws or regulations. For Campaign data, Allkeyshop Network Users have control of the purpose for collecting data, and the duration for which the Personal Data may be kept. When a User’s account is terminated, deleted or expired, all Personal Data collected through the platform will be deleted, as required by applicable law.

###  **Privacy Controls & Choices**

Allkeyshop Network Websites Communication: Our Customers, Site Visitors and Users have a choice about how we use their personal data to get in touch with them and may choose to opt-out at any time by unsubscribing or changing their account settings.   Newsletter Users Notifications: We provide an easy mechanism for opt-ing out of any communication from campaigns inside the Post Entry Email. You can simply selec the Unsubscribe links in the footer. Users Social Accounts: We provide a mechanism for every users to remove any linked social accounts from Allkeyshop via the Profil page. Your Rights: We provide all Customers, Visitors and Users of our Site with the opportunity to request access, correction, restriction, deletion, data portability or oppose to any personal information that has previously been provided to us in connection with the use of our Website, as required by law. You can send us an email to [support@Allkeyshop.com](mailto:support@Allkeyshop.com). We may request specific information from you to confirm your identity.

###  **Allkeyshop Network Data Protection Officer**

Allkeyshop Network has a Data Protection Officer who is responsible for matters relating to privacy and data protection. This Data Protection Officer can be reached at the following address: Allkeyshop Limited 31 / F., Chinachem Century Tower, 178, rue Gloucester, Wanchai, Hong Kong Mail: Support@allkeyshop.com

##  **Compliance With Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act**

Because the nature of our Site and Services does not appeal to children under the age of 13, Allkeyshop Network does not knowingly acquire or receive personal data from children under 13. We do not intentionally process any information, including Personal Data, from children or other individuals who are not legally able to use our Site and Services. If we later learn that any user of our Service is under the age of 13 and that we have obtained his/her Personal Data, we will promptly delete it from our database and will take further steps to restrict that individual from future access to our Services, unless we are legally obligated to retain such data. If you are a parent or legal guardian of a child under 13 and believe that we might have any information from or about such child, please contact us at the email or mailing address provided at the end of this Privacy Policy.

##  **Business Transfers**

In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that are transferred. Moreover, if Allkeyshop Network, or substantially all of its assets were to be acquired, or in the unlikely event that Allkeyshop Network goes out of business, customer information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquire of Allkeyshop Network or its assets may continue to use your Personal Information as set forth in this policy.

##  **Changes To This Privacy Policy**

Allkeyshop Network has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

##  **Your Acceptance Of These Terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and terms of service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

##  **Contacting Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at [Support@allkeyshop.com](mailto:Support@allkeyshop.com) This document was last updated on May 23th, 2018
